<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MSAdministrator</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MSAdministrator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 20:44:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add and Remove Users to Ad Groups With Group Policy</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 20:44:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description>Group Policy allows you to add and remove users to an Active Directory (AD) group. Using this feature improves security because you can ensure that high-risk security groups only contain the users that you specify via Group Policy.
Read More</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 21:49:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/projects/</guid>
      <description> WriteLogEntry: A PowerShell helper function to create and write information to a log file PowerShell Phishing Response Toolkit: This PowerShell Module is designed to send notifications to hosting companies that host phishing URLs by utilizing the major WHOIS/RDAP Abuse Point of Contact (POC) information CreateProfile: PowerShell Module that uses WINAPI to create system profiles GetGithubRepository: This PowerShell function will download Github files without using Git PoshZD: A PowerShell Module to interact with the ZenDesk ticketing system PSRegistry: A PowerShell Module that replaces the reg commands using the WIN_API POSH-NotifyGroupOwnerManager  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>/page/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 21:47:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/presentations/</guid>
      <description> I have included a list below of my previous presentations and any relevant links. This will be continually updated moving forward:
Presentation Slides  Basics of Incident Handling Securing Windows with Group Policy  Past Presentations  SECURING WINDOWS WITH (SOME) GROUP POLICY – 2018 SHOWMECON SECURING WINDOWS WITH (SOME) GROUP POLICY – 2018 BSIDESKC MOTIVATIONS &amp;amp; TACTICS OF PHISHING – 2017 MORENET ANNUAL CONFERENCE SECURING WINDOWS WITH GROUP POLICY – 2017 DERBYCON BASICS OF INCIDENT RESPONSE – 2017 BSIDESSTL (2) HALF DAY POWERSHELL TRAINING COURSE FOR 80+ - 2017 MU VET MED PPRT: POWERSHELL PHISHING RESPONSE TOOLKIT – 2016 SHOWMECON PPRT: POWERSHELL PHISHING RESPONSE TOOLKIT – 2016 CIRCLE CITY CON SECURING WINDOWS WITH GROUP POLICY – 2015 MORENET ANNUAL CONFERENCE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Away From Wordpress</title>
      <link>/article/moving-away-from-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 12:55:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/article/moving-away-from-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Hello Everyone, I have decided this past weekend to final move completely away from WordPress for my blog; and I&amp;rsquo;m 100% excited for this transition! I have decided to use GitHub Pages for my new blog.
I plan on migrating content to this new locaton, but in the meantime if you find any missing content that you have seen previously then please let me know and I will get it moved over ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 12:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Josh&amp;rsquo;s primary focus is in Windows security and PowerShell automation. He is a GIAC Certified Windows Security Administrator (GCWN) and GIAC Certified Forensic Analyst (GCFA). You can reach Josh at MSAdministrator.com or on Twitter at @MS_dministrator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>