<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>atomic-red-team on Lets Automate It</title>
    <link>https://letsautomate.it/tags/atomic-red-team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in atomic-red-team on Lets Automate It</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 11:54:39 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://letsautomate.it/tags/atomic-red-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Red Team Testing With Swimlane</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/atomic-red-team-testing-with-swimlane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 11:54:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/atomic-red-team-testing-with-swimlane/</guid>
      <description>Today, Swimlane is excited to announce that we are releasing a new SSP (Swimlane Solutions Package) for use within the Swimlane platform. This SSP will enable organizations to automate the testing of their defenses using Atomic Red Team using our new open-source project called atomic-operator.
When using this SSP organizations can gain an understanding of their defensive posture against tests mapped to MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques. By using this use case you can correlate detections of these tests against their existing automation and log sources thus giving them fast feedback on their defensive posture based on tests available within Atomic Red Team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Attck Testing With Soar and Atomic Red Team</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/automating-attck-testing-with-soar-and-atomic-red-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 12:33:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/automating-attck-testing-with-soar-and-atomic-red-team/</guid>
      <description>MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK is the defacto framework for organizations to measure their defense posture. ATT&amp;amp;CK provides categorical verticals in the form of tactics, which align to the common methodologies attackers use. Within these verticals are a set (and subsets) of common ways in which attackers accomplish a tactic (vertical). These are known as techniques.
Some techniques may be common across multiple operating systems. This usually equates to a broad definition of a technique.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
