<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devops on Lets Automate It</title>
    <link>https://letsautomate.it/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devops on Lets Automate It</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 14:40:36 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://letsautomate.it/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Every Security Team Is a Software Team Now</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/every-security-team-is-a-software-team-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 14:40:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/every-security-team-is-a-software-team-now/</guid>
      <description>Building and facilitating a culture with continuous collaboration between engineers and security forces is becoming the new philosophy in security, which is why I am stoked for this year&amp;rsquo;s Black Hat USA keynote speaker: Dino Dai Zovi, staff security engineer at Square.
&amp;ldquo;Every Security Team is a Software Team Now&amp;rdquo; promises to dive into the latest iteration of security operations as current security teams morph into in-house security software teams, delivering multi-vertical value through self-service platforms and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey InfoSec, What Are You Doing to Protect Your DevOps Teams</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/hey-infosec-what-are-you-doing-to-protect-your-devops-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 14:29:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/hey-infosec-what-are-you-doing-to-protect-your-devops-teams/</guid>
      <description>DevOps, serverless applications and containers are just a few of the latest advancements in a developer&amp;rsquo;s toolbox. For development teams, this means that the time to market (TTM) is faster—especially for Agile teams. So, how and what are security operations teams doing to ensure that security is keeping pace with this rapid development? Most are attempting to incorporate a security engineer within their development teams—which is a great first step—but there are multiple layers that you need to ensure you are protecting your organization beyond your source-code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
