<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automation on Lets Automate It</title>
    <link>https://letsautomate.it/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in automation on Lets Automate It</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 12:33:03 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://letsautomate.it/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automating Attck Testing With Soar and Atomic Red Team</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/automating-attck-testing-with-soar-and-atomic-red-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 12:33:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/automating-attck-testing-with-soar-and-atomic-red-team/</guid>
      <description>MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK is the defacto framework for organizations to measure their defense posture. ATT&amp;amp;CK provides categorical verticals in the form of tactics, which align to the common methodologies attackers use. Within these verticals are a set (and subsets) of common ways in which attackers accomplish a tactic (vertical). These are known as techniques.
Some techniques may be common across multiple operating systems. This usually equates to a broad definition of a technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making MITRE ATT&amp;CK Actionable</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/making-mitre-attck-actionable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 12:33:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/making-mitre-attck-actionable/</guid>
      <description>The Swimlane Deep Dive team is excited to announce the release of pyattck 2.0 and an equivalent PowerShell version called PSAttck. These open-source tools provide security operations centers (SOCs), defenders and offensive security teams with external data points that enrich MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK by providing potential commands, queries and even detections for specific techniques. Additionally, these data points enable context related to specific attacker actors or groups, as well as details about different tools used by malicious actors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responding to Insider Threats With Soar</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/responding-to-insider-threats-with-soar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 12:37:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/responding-to-insider-threats-with-soar/</guid>
      <description>Insider threats occur when an individual with ties to an organization misuses their access for malicious intent, such as stealing intellectual property or other data. Detecting insider threats can be difficult. But by using a security information and event management (SIEM) system or data loss prevention (DLP) products, you can create alerts to detect the exfiltration of data leaving your organization that is unauthorized or unexpected.
Once you have detected these events, your security operations center (SOC) needs to investigate rapidly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify Malicious Domains Using Soar</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/identify-malicious-domains-using-soar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 12:38:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/identify-malicious-domains-using-soar/</guid>
      <description>Domain Squatting, typosquatting and IDN homograph attacks are commonplace when it comes to phishing and other forms of social engineering. Attackers use domain squatting and typosquatting of domains to trick users into providing their credentials, distribute malware, harm an organization’s reputation, or otherwise maliciously impersonate a legitimate domain. We&amp;rsquo;ve discussed this topic before and have developed a unique use case with Swimlane to detect this malicious activity automatically.
Recently, we began to monitor domains related to coronavirus (COVID-19), knowing there would be an increase in traffic to research the outbreak, which could be exploited by bad actors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Dont Have Windows 7 in Your Environment Do You</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/you-dont-have-windows-7-in-your-environment-do-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 12:40:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/you-dont-have-windows-7-in-your-environment-do-you/</guid>
      <description>Today is the day. Microsoft Windows 7 is officially end-of-life (EOL). The Windows 7 operating system was released on October 22, 2009. For 10 years now, IT and system administrators around the globe have relied on their trusty old Windows 7 OS. I mean, it was a step beyond Windows XP for sure. With EOL here, have you migrated all of your systems to Windows 10?
If you have not migrated, you definitely should.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Security Team Is a Software Team Now</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/every-security-team-is-a-software-team-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 14:40:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/every-security-team-is-a-software-team-now/</guid>
      <description>Building and facilitating a culture with continuous collaboration between engineers and security forces is becoming the new philosophy in security, which is why I am stoked for this year&amp;rsquo;s Black Hat USA keynote speaker: Dino Dai Zovi, staff security engineer at Square.
&amp;ldquo;Every Security Team is a Software Team Now&amp;rdquo; promises to dive into the latest iteration of security operations as current security teams morph into in-house security software teams, delivering multi-vertical value through self-service platforms and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender Advanced Threat Detection Queries</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/microsoft-defender-advanced-threat-detection-queries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 14:37:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/microsoft-defender-advanced-threat-detection-queries/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I shared on Twitter how you could run a query to detect if a user has clicked on a link within their Outlook using Microsoft Defender Advanced Threat Protection (MDATP). If you are not familiar, MDATP is available within your Microsoft 365 E5 license and is an enhancement to the traditional Windows Defender you might be used to.
What is Microsoft Defender Advanced Threat Protection? Microsoft says that “Microsoft Defender Advanced Threat Protection is a platform designed to help enterprise networks prevent, detect, investigate, and respond to advanced threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimlane&#39;s Research Teams Open Sources pyattck</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlanes-research-teams-open-sources-pyattck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 14:34:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlanes-research-teams-open-sources-pyattck/</guid>
      <description>As security teams adopt the Mitre ATT&amp;amp;CK Framework to help them identify gaps in their defenses, having a way to identify what malware and tools are being used by specific actors or groups becomes more critical. Additionally, having a way to identify these relationships programatically is even more critical.
Today, we are excited to announce the Swimlane research team has released pyattck — a Python package to interact with the Mitre ATT&amp;amp;CK Framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimlane Open Sources graphish to Help SecOps Teams</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlane-open-sources-graphish-to-help-secops-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 14:31:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlane-open-sources-graphish-to-help-secops-teams/</guid>
      <description>While having a conversation on Twitter about Microsoft Graph API I was convinced that the traditional Exchange eDiscovery features were not available in the Microsoft Graph API. Boy was I wrong.
After stumbling across a few endpoints I had not seen previously, I decided to write a python package called graphish. graphish is an open-source python package Swimlane is open-sourcing that will enable IT, security operations (SecOps), developers and others to search and delete email messages from mailboxes using the Microsoft Graph API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimlane Research Team Open Sources py-ews</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlane-research-team-open-sources-py-ews/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 14:27:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/swimlane-research-team-open-sources-py-ews/</guid>
      <description>Phishing impacts every organization, and security operations (SecOps) teams need to act quickly to remediate and prevent unknown threats within their email infrastructure. To help combat these threats, the Swimlane research team has open sourced py-ews to enable security and IT teams to interact with Microsoft Exchange Web Services (EWS) using Python.
Why py-ews? Organizations continue to battle against malicious phishing emails in their email environments, but security and IT teams have limited visibility into what currently resides in their users&#39; mailboxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate Employee Off Boarding Process With Swimlane</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/automate-employee-off-boarding-process-with-swimlane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 14:25:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/automate-employee-off-boarding-process-with-swimlane/</guid>
      <description>As more organizations discontinue internal services and begin adopting an increasing number of third-party *aaS-based services, ensuring the appropriate access is revoked in a timely manner is critical. By using our new employee off-boarding use case, you can automatically gather historical data, add a user to a monitoring watch list, and finally remove access when it is time to off-board an employee.
The employee off-boarding use case contains two distinct applications to assist an organization with managing their employee off-boarding process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Malware Analysis and Reverse Engineering With Soar</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/automated-malware-analysis-and-reverse-engineering-with-soar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 14:10:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/automated-malware-analysis-and-reverse-engineering-with-soar/</guid>
      <description>We all know that security operations (SecOps) teams are overwhelmed by the extreme number of alerts they receive on a daily basis. Organizations are being attacked from all fronts, whether they know it or not. These attacks vary from social engineering, malicious emails, vulnerable services and applications, misconfiguration (job fatigue), etc.
Traditionally in a security operations center (SOC), malware analysis—more specifically reverse engineering—is conducted by a highly trained member of the security team (depending on your size, this may be multiple individuals).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup a Hugo Website on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/article/how-to-setup-a-hugo-website-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 16:07:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/article/how-to-setup-a-hugo-website-on-github/</guid>
      <description>I recently transitioned my blog over to GitHub Pages from WordPress. I was using the free version from WordPress.org and I wanted more granular control over the layout. Additionally, I wanted to automate my blog publishing and social media notifications; the free version of WordPress didn&amp;rsquo;t meet my needs. So I looked around and eventually fell in love with Hugo! This post outlines how to go about setting up a GitHub Pages website/blog using Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
