<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Lets Automate It</title>
    <link>https://letsautomate.it/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Lets Automate It</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 08:47:39 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://letsautomate.it/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Projects</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/page/open-source-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 08:47:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/page/open-source-projects/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of open-source projects I have started or contributed heavily to:
 speedtweet  This docker-compose project will check your internet speed against a specified threshold and if below it will tweet at the provided account about your current internet speeds. Type: Docker   slack-url-utils  slack-url-utils is a slash command utility for Slack that obfuscates, deobfuscates, gets DNS information, and submits IOCs to AlienVault for a given URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/page/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 21:47:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/page/presentations/</guid>
      <description>I have included a list below of my previous presentations and any relevant links. This will be continually updated moving forward:
Presentation Slides  Making MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Actionable (gif) (pdf) py-ews: A cross platform python package to interact with Exchange Web Services Hunting Phish Kits PowerShell vs Python: A side-by-side comparison Basics of Incident Handling Securing Windows with Group Policy  Past Presentations  Making MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Actionable - 2020 Hacker Halted py-ews: A cross platform python package to interact with Exchange Web Services - 2019 BSidesSTL Hunting Phish Kits - 2019 DerbyCon PowerShell vs Python: A side-by-side comparison - 2019 BSides Springfield (Missouri) - No Video SECURING WINDOWS WITH (SOME) GROUP POLICY – 2018 SHOWMECON SECURING WINDOWS WITH (SOME) GROUP POLICY – 2018 BSIDESKC MOTIVATIONS &amp;amp; TACTICS OF PHISHING – 2017 MORENET ANNUAL CONFERENCE SECURING WINDOWS WITH GROUP POLICY – 2017 DERBYCON BASICS OF INCIDENT RESPONSE – 2017 BSIDESSTL (2) HALF DAY POWERSHELL TRAINING COURSE FOR 80+ - 2017 MU VET MED PPRT: POWERSHELL PHISHING RESPONSE TOOLKIT – 2016 SHOWMECON PPRT: POWERSHELL PHISHING RESPONSE TOOLKIT – 2016 CIRCLE CITY CON SECURING WINDOWS WITH GROUP POLICY – 2015 MORENET ANNUAL CONFERENCE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://letsautomate.it/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 12:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://letsautomate.it/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Josh&amp;rsquo;s primary focus is in Windows security and PowerShell automation. He is a GIAC Certified Windows Security Administrator (GCWN) and GIAC Certified Forensic Analyst (GCFA). You can reach Josh at MSAdministrator.com or on Twitter at @MS_dministrator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
